Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=The Demon=
=الشيطان=
=Episode 15=
=الحلقة 15=
Buns for sale!
كعكات للبيع!
Freshly steamed bun!
كعكة مطهوة على البخار طازجة!
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
Steaming hot buns!
الكعك الساخن جداً!
Fresh buns!
كعكات طازجة!
Let me try.
دعني أحاول.
Come and try them.
تعال وجربهم.
The buns look delicious,
الكعك يبدو لذيذا،
Dayao.
مع السلامة.
Since when do you like eating buns?
منذ متى تحب أكل الكعك؟
Honestly, I'd like to eat one right now.
بصراحة، أريد أن آكل واحدة الآن.
It's my fault
إنه خطئي
for dragging you along.
لسحبك معك.
Maybe
ربما
I'm not suited
أنا لست مناسبا
for this guardian post.
لهذا المنصب الوصي.
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
When I master
عندما أتقن
the spell to eat once and stay full ten times,
تعويذة الأكل مرة واحدة والشبع عشر مرات،
this is just a small matter.
هذه مجرد مسألة صغيرة.
Come on!
تعال!
Something is happening at the Shen Residence today.
هناك شيء يحدث في مقر إقامة شين اليوم.
They're handing out wedding sweets.
إنهم يوزعون حلوى الزفاف.
Let's go see.
دعنا نذهب لنرى.
- Shen Residence?
- سكن شين؟
I'm coming too.
انا قادم أيضا
Dayao, wait for me.
دياو، انتظرني.
They're coming out.
إنهم يخرجون.
Such a perfect match.
إنها مباراة مثالية.
(Shen Residence) They are truly made for each other.
(مقر شين) لقد خلقوا حقا لبعضهم البعض.
Look!
ينظر!
Young Master Shen and Princess Huaiyang are getting engaged.
السيد الشاب شين والأميرة هوايانج سيتزوجان.
What a fine couple.
يا له من زوجين رائعين.
A match made in heaven.
مباراة صنعت في الجنة.
Thank you, everyone.
شكرا للجميع.
We're giving out candies.
نحن نوزع الحلوى.
Oh, thank you!
أوه، شكرا لك!
Thank you, Your Highness.
شكرا لك يا صاحب السمو.
Over here! Over here!
هنا! هنا!
I want some too!
أريد بعضًا أيضًا!
Over here!
هنا!
Over here.
هنا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I want some too.
أريد بعضًا أيضًا.
They're such a fine pair.
إنهم زوج رائع.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Over here.
هنا.
This is mine.
هذه ملكي.
It wasn't easy for me to get this.
لم يكن من السهل بالنسبة لي الحصول على هذا.
(Shen Residence)
(سكن شين)
Rong Momo.
رونغ مومو.
Let me have some.
دعني آخذ بعضًا منها.
Can you tell me
هل يمكن أن تخبرني
what "engaged" means?
ماذا يعني "مخطوبة"؟
It means the man
يعني الرجل
and woman fancy each other.
والنساء يعجبون ببعضهم البعض.
Speak so I can understand.
تكلم حتى أفهم.
It means Mr. Shen
وهذا يعني السيد شين
will now
سوف الان
be the Princess's husband.
كن زوج الأميرة.
Cheater.
غشاش.
Dayao,
صباح الخير،
don't go near them.
لا تقترب منهم
There are too many people.
هناك الكثير من الناس.
We need to think this through
نحن بحاجة إلى التفكير في هذا الأمر
and discuss this.
وناقش هذا الأمر.
Wangchen,
وانجشين,
I'm a little tired.
أنا متعب قليلاً.
Let's go back.
دعونا نعود.
All right.
حسنًا.
You must be tired, Your Highness.
لا بد أنك متعب، يا صاحب السمو.
Not at all.
مُطْلَقاً.
(Shen Residence)
(سكن شين)
Master,
يتقن،
I sense demonic activity
أشعر بنشاط شيطاني
beyond this bridge.
وراء هذا الجسر.
We're already too late.
لقد تأخرنا بالفعل.
I've already checked.
لقد قمت بالتحقق بالفعل.
A family of four has been drained of their essence,
لقد تم استنزاف جوهر عائلة مكونة من أربعة أفراد،
not a bone left.
لم يبق عظم.
We must keep this quiet,
يجب علينا أن نبقي هذا الأمر هادئا،
or Moyuan City will fall into panic.
وإلا فإن مدينة مويوان سوف تقع في حالة من الذعر.
Yes, Master.
نعم سيدي.
I'm afraid there's big trouble in the city.
أخشى أن تكون هناك مشكلة كبيرة في المدينة.
Then I'll report to the City Lord
ثم سأبلغ إلى سيد المدينة
and organize a hunt.
وتنظيم الصيد.
No.
لا.
Do not startle the enemy.
لا تخيف العدو.
Leave this to me.
اترك هذا لي.
Dayao, you're here again.
دياو، أنت هنا مرة أخرى.
Why don't we leave this place?
لماذا لا نترك هذا المكان؟
The people of Moyuan City
سكان مدينة مويوان
are too complicated.
معقدة للغاية.
This place is simply not for us.
هذا المكان ليس لنا على الاطلاق.
Let's return to the Demon Fort.
دعونا نعود إلى حصن الشيطان.
That's our true home.
هذا هو منزلنا الحقيقي.
Don't talk to me.
لا تتحدث معي.
I need to think.
أحتاج إلى التفكير.
At a time like this,
في وقت كهذا،
what's there to think about?
ماذا هناك للتفكير فيه؟
Shen Wangchen already made his choice.
لقد اتخذ شين وانجشين خياره بالفعل.
Who does he think he is?
من يعتقد نفسه؟
It's making me furious.
إنه يجعلني غاضبًا.
And that Jiang Li too.
وهذا جيانج لي أيضًا.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
I don't need Jiang Li either.
أنا لا أحتاج إلى جيانج لي أيضًا.
Let them have whoever they want.
دعهم يمتلكون من يريدون.
We'll go back to the Demon Fort.
سوف نعود إلى حصن الشيطان.
But I can't shake the feeling
ولكن لا أستطيع التخلص من هذا الشعور
that Shen Wangchen isn't like that.
أن شين وانجشين ليس كذلك.
Why do you think he...
لماذا تعتقد أنه...
Why do you carry red beans with you?
لماذا تحمل الفاصوليا الحمراء معك؟
They are as hard as stones.
إنهم قساة كالحجارة.
Yet, you've turned them into something so soft and sweet.
ومع ذلك، لقد حولتهم إلى شيء ناعم وحلو للغاية.
Because red beans are said
لأن الفاصوليا الحمراء يقال
to be the fruit of longing.
أن تكون ثمرة الشوق.
I learn something new.
أتعلم شيئا جديدا.
(Then)
(ثم)
(can I have another bowl?)
(هل يمكنني الحصول على وعاء آخر؟)
(As much as you like.)
(بقدر ما تريد.)
I trust him.
انا اثق به.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Momo?
يكتب؟
I've finally found you.
لقد وجدتك أخيرا.
Shouldn't you be enjoying
ألا ينبغي عليك أن تستمتع؟
the Princess's riches
ثروات الأميرة
with Shen Wangchen?
مع شين وانغشن؟
Momo.
يكتب.
You must be starving these few days.
لا بد أنك جائع هذه الأيام القليلة.
Look what I brought.
انظر ماذا أحضرت.
What took you so long?
ما الذي أخذ منك كل هذا الوقت؟
I've gone days
لقد مضت أيام
without a proper meal.
بدون وجبة مناسبة.
Forgive me, Momo.
سامحني يا مومو.
I know you have suffered these past few days.
أعلم أنك عانيت في الأيام القليلة الماضية.
That wretched princess
تلك الأميرة البائسة
never lets us out of her sight.
لا تدعنا نخرج من نظرها أبدًا.
I barely managed to sneak away.
تمكنت بالكاد من التسلل بعيدا.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Eat first.
تناول الطعام أولا.
Here.
هنا.
Slowly, don't choke yourself.
ببطء، لا تخنق نفسك.
So, does this mean Mr. Shen and the Princess
إذن، هل هذا يعني أن السيد شين والأميرة
will always be together?
سوف نكون دائما معا؟
Who knows what Young Master truly thinks?
من يعرف ما يفكر فيه الشاب حقًا؟
But I can't stand that Princess.
ولكنني لا أستطيع أن أتحمل تلك الأميرة.
Then does that mean
ثم هل هذا يعني
we can't
لا يمكننا
be together anymore?
هل سنكون معاً بعد الآن؟
I thought
اعتقدت
if Dayao and Mr. Shen
إذا داياو والسيد شين
could get married,
يمكن أن يتزوج
then maybe we could too.
فربما يمكننا أن نفعل ذلك أيضًا.
We?
نحن؟
If you don't want it, just say so.
إذا كنت لا تريد ذلك، فقط قل ذلك.
You didn't have to run!
لم يكن عليك الركض!
Momo.
يكتب.
Leave me alone.
اتركني وحدي.
I don't want to see you.
لا أريد رؤيتك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I should've proposed first.
كان ينبغي لي أن أتقدم بالطلب أولاً.
Momo, look.
مومو، انظري.
This is all I own.
هذا كل ما أملكه.
It may not be much.
ربما لا يكون كثيرا.
But I promise
ولكنني أعدك
I'll cook
سأطبخ
whatever you want to eat.
كل ما تريد أن تأكله.
I'm serious.
أنا جادة.
I'll give everything
سأعطي كل شيء
just to make you smile.
فقط لأجعلك تبتسم.
The truth is,
الحقيقة هي
since the very first moment I saw you,
منذ اللحظة الأولى التي رأيتك فيها،
I was already in love.
لقد كنت في الحب بالفعل.
What if
ماذا إذا
Mr. Shen doesn't agree?
السيد شين لا يوافق؟
Who cares?
من يهتم؟
Momo,
يكتب،
let's spend our lives together.
دعونا نقضي حياتنا معًا.
What do you say?
ماذا تقول؟
Of course!
بالطبع!
♪Love is hard to comprehend in this world♪
???هل الحب صعب فهمه في هذا العالم؟؟؟
♪Yearning for love feels the longest♪
???هل يعتبر الشوق للحب هو الأطول؟
♪Who comes with me on my long journey?♪
???من سيأتي معي في رحلتي الطويلة ؟؟؟؟
♪Where can I rest after picking up the cold branches?♪
أين يمكنني أن أستريح بعد التقاط الأغصان الباردة ؟؟؟؟
♪I'm willing to trade all my smiles from the past♪
???هل أنا على استعداد لتبادل كل ابتساماتي من الماضي؟؟؟
Wangchen, look.
وانغتشين، انظر.
The garden is in full bloom
الحديقة في ازدهار كامل
for you.
لك.
Just like my heart,
تماما مثل قلبي،
beating only for you.
الضرب من أجلك فقط
You're flattering me, Your Highness.
أنت تملقني، سموّك.
These flowers are nature's beauty.
هذه الزهور هي جمال الطبيعة.
It has nothing to do with me.
لا علاقة لي بهذا الأمر.
Wangchen.
وانجتشن.
From the moment I first saw you,
منذ اللحظة الأولى التي رأيتك فيها،
I...
أنا...
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Don't forget I suffer from a strange illness.
لا تنسوا أنني أعاني من مرض غريب.
But...
لكن...
But I can't be bothered with all that anymore.
لكن لم أعد أستطيع أن أهتم بكل ذلك بعد الآن.
(Shen Residence)
(سكن شين)
♪Where did I lose my direction?♪
???أين فقدت اتجاهي ؟؟؟؟
♪Only emptiness is left♪
???لم يبق إلا الفراغ؟؟؟
♪Restless, sleepless, we part ways♪
???أرق، لا ينام، نحن نفترق؟؟؟
♪As sorrow slowly grows within♪
"كما ينمو الحزن ببطء في الداخل"
♪Tears can't heal, smiles still ache♪
???الدموع لا يمكن أن تشفى، والابتسامات لا تزال تؤلمني؟؟؟
♪Because my heart's with you♪
???لأن قلبي معك؟؟؟
♪Your gaze melted the haze♪
"نظرتك أذابت الضباب"
♪Waiting so long for your return♪
???هل انتظرت عودتك لفترة طويلة؟
♪The setting sun reminds me of you♪
???غروب الشمس يذكرني بك؟؟؟
♪If the clear sky is torn by storm and rain one day♪
ماذا لو تمزقت السماء الصافية بفعل العاصفة والمطر في يوم من الأيام؟
♪Tears will flow♪
???هل ستتدفق الدموع؟؟؟
♪I will still wait here with no regrets♪
???سوف أظل أنتظر هنا دون أي ندم؟؟؟
♪Waiting so long for your return♪
???هل انتظرت عودتك لفترة طويلة؟
♪The setting sun reminds me of you♪
???غروب الشمس يذكرني بك؟؟؟
♪In the amber desert, you turn away with tears in your eyes♪
???في الصحراء الكهرمانية، تبتعد والدموع في عينيك؟؟؟
♪I'll welcome you back in a red dress♪
???سأرحب بك مرة أخرى بفستان أحمر؟؟؟
♪Waiting forever with no regrets♪
???الانتظار إلى الأبد دون أي ندم؟؟؟